[{"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示河马数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": 6}], "answeritem": [7, 6], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示斑马数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": 6}], "answeritem": [6, 8], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示猪数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": 6}], "answeritem": [6, 9], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示小狗数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": 6}], "answeritem": [6, 10], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示猪数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": 7}], "answeritem": [6, 7], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示袋鼠数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": 7}], "answeritem": [7, 8], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示长颈鹿数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": 7}], "answeritem": [7, 9], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示小狗数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": 7}], "answeritem": [7, 10], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示河马数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": 8}], "answeritem": [8, 6], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示斑马数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": 8}], "answeritem": [8, 7], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示牛数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": 8}], "answeritem": [9, 8], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示老虎数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": 8}], "answeritem": [10, 8], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示长颈鹿数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": 9}], "answeritem": [6, 9], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [9], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示牛数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": 9}], "answeritem": [9, 7], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [9], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示犀牛数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/犀牛_R1.svg", "num": 9}], "answeritem": [8, 9], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [9], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示长颈鹿数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": 9}], "answeritem": [9, 10], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [9], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示斑马数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": 10}], "answeritem": [10, 6], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [10], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示袋鼠数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": 10}], "answeritem": [7, 10], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [10], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示大象数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": 10}], "answeritem": [8, 10], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [10], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数一数", "stem": "表示小狗数量的圆", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": 10}], "answeritem": [10, 9], "type": "animal-num-sum"}], "answers": [10], "knowledges": ["10以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-9-01"}]